Welcome to ACI Advanced Characterization and Instrumentation.
Before introducing ACI in more detail,
this slide provides a quick overview of the ISCE² organizational structure.
Here, you can see where ACI sits within the Institute.
ACI is led by our Division Director,
Andrew Lim.
In the next few slides,
I will introduce our team and highlight the key analytical capabilities and
shared scientific resources that we offer.
ACI is organised into three technical domains,
chromatography and mass spectrometry, X-ray spectroscopy and microscopy,
and NMR, physical and thermal characterisation.
Together, our domain leads and staff manage a broad range of shared
scientific resources and provide analytical and characterisation support,
as well as technical training,
to our research community.
Beyond supporting our internal R&D activities,
we also extend our capabilities to industry partners,
providing services such as material characterisation,
failure diagnostics, method development, consultancy,
and collaboration.
Through these capabilities, we aim to provide practical analytical solutions to support
different research and industry needs.
The ACI division is led by our division director,
Andrew Lim, and Ong Li Li as the Division Deputy Director.
And it comprises three technical domains,
each led by our respective domain lead.
The Chromatography and Mass Spectrometry domain is led by Mr.
Ong Wai Chung, supported by our instrument specialists,
Ng Fu Song and Tan Kuan Yi.
The X-ray Spectroscopy and Microscopy domain is led by Ms.
Angeline Seo, together with three senior domain specialists,
Wang Zhan, Chia Sze Chen,
and Cao Xun, who specialize in XPS,
XRD and TEM respectively.
Ong Li Li also served as the domain lead of NMR,
Physical and Thermal Characterisation, supported by instrument specialists Yeo Wen Cong and
Kuan Kai Cong.
Beyond our analytical and characterisation work,
ACI also plays an important role in managing shared scientific resources across
the Institute.
Our responsibilities include equipment booking,
utilisation and charging, demand aggregation,
scientific equipment and systems refresh,
and equipment lifecycle management.
We also support digitalisation and sustainability initiatives.
Together, these activities help ensure that our scientific resources are effectively managed,
optimised, and kept relevant to support the evolving research needs across the
Institute.